[{"answer": "Yes, I thought she did.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Gloria, what did you think?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, it means that there's this -- as Joaquin has said many times -- he's campaigning for Congress these days -- but this sort of infrastructure of opportunity, of strong public schools, of good universities, of student aid, of those things that it takes to experience opportunity in America.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "How do you reinforce the kind of story that you guys can tell America?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, what I think is that when folks compare where the nation was when President Obama took office -- and you heard several speakers say that -- losing 750,000 to 800,000 jobs a month, and then you compare where we are now, of 29 straight months of private sector job growth, 4.5 million new jobs -- that I'm confident he's going to lay out the case very convincingly for why, even though we haven't made the -- we're not where we want to be.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Are you pleased to see that?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, I think that to have Jimmy Carter -- I think he emphasizes foreign policy, and I think President Obama has a very good foreign policy.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Governor Rendell, Governor Richardson, thank you both very much.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "If I'm an independent voter, I'm saying, What in God's name is he talking about?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, it was bittersweet, once (ph) because he wasn't there to be there in person, but he was there in spirit.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What did you make of it, watching from wherever you were in the convention hall?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I guess I share your sense of irony on that.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "IZZA: It's better, but I'll be honest.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Is it better now?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Pride.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What was your -- your feeling when you finished up?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Well, we have a commitment through all faith traditions that our values are reflected in our policy, and that means that we should look out for the least of these, that we should fight for the middle class, that we should help everyone in America have an opportunity to be successful and...", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Oh, of course not.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Right, but was the word \"God\" deliberately taken out, or was it a mistake?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "We have a platform that actually reflects the values of many faith traditions and...", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "It was a mistake?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "We are focused on continuing to run the most significant dynamic grassroots presidential campaign.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Are you worried about that?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I'd be gathering around her.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Wouldn't that be nice?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Deservedly so.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Debbie?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "No, because we still have 23 million people unemployed and I think that if you were going --", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Would you agree, as I said earlier, would you agree that we are better off than we were three and a half years ago?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, a couple of things there, Piers.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Or is it a lot more likely that it was for political expedience?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No, but you would have to ask -- I think that we have a lot bigger problems to worry about than what the Democrats are doing with their web videos.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Was it wrong of Democrats to use that footage, do you think, in a video to Senator Kennedy?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "No, we're talking about the things that the Democrats aren't.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "When you are Mitt Romeny's communication director and you're here in Charlotte, North Carolina in the middle of thousands of Democrats, is it a lonely place to find yourself, Gail?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Sure, you're going to see blaming, you're going to see scapegoats.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Well, their argument is now that they inherited the mother of all policies and you don't dispute that?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Oh, great.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "A win?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "It was more powerful than I thought.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Having watched it now, what did you think?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Right, right.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "She's not going to stand on a platform in front of billions of people and start banging on about all the negatives, is she?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Well, you know, one of the things we saw with the Democrats this weekend and it goes to the platform it's this is not sort of a, you know, point by point soft to the right wing the way the Republican platform has been.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Hilary?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Well, there are stats on both sides.", "docId": "120904pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Hilary, how do you dispute the fact that it doesn't look like we are in better shape in America?", "qSentId": 563}]